<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PORTFOLIO on Harry Sarson</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in PORTFOLIO on Harry Sarson</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><copyright>© Harry Sarson</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uncertainty Propagtion Masters Project</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/masters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/masters/</guid><description>A thesis summing up my masters (part IIB) project. Writen in the early summer of 2019. During the year long project I studied uncertainty propagation — methods that encode information about potential errors in data originating from the real world and produce estimates of how wrong the output of calculations using that data might be.
The thesis describes a framework for uncertainty propagation and sketches an extension to the RISC-V instruction set architecture.</description></item><item><title>SarsonWedding</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/sarsonwedding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/sarsonwedding/</guid><description>A simple but visually pleasing website to provide information to family and friends. To view the website you will need the password 050621 (the date of the wedding). The website has two main parts, an entry page written in html and typescript and the main website written in elm.
The most interesting part of the website is its password protection. The source of the website is hosted in a public git repo but all the interesting information is encrypted (see the encrypted.</description></item><item><title>Elm Test</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/elm-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/elm-test/</guid><description>I maintained the npm elm-test package. The test runner, widely used by the elm community, has recently received some much needed contributions its code base. It was a huge privilege to steer the project back into active development.</description></item><item><title>Welsh Whacker</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/welsh-whacker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/welsh-whacker/</guid><description>Part of an advertising pitch to Visit Wales designed by by Helen + Phil. ‘The Welsh Whacker’ takes the stress out of trying to spell Welsh towns. It matches any search to the Welsh destination with the closest spelling!
I built the Welsh Whacker as a single page application using the elm programming language. I took special care to encode all necessary state in the page URL so that links can be effortlessly shared.</description></item><item><title>Prime Image</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/prime-image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/prime-image/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Circles</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/circles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/circles/</guid><description>Create wonderful pictures using only circles. Create and move points to change the pattern. Click anywhere to add a point, drag a point over to the bin to remove.</description></item><item><title>Tank</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/tank/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/tank/</guid><description>Drive your very own tank around a vast map and score points by hitting the target. Hover your mouse over commands to see the keyboard shortcut.
However keep an eye on your fuel; if it runs out the game&amp;rsquo;s over. To refuel, drive over to the refueling area and stop your engine. Make sure the tank is facing the right way!</description></item><item><title>Circles</title><link>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/curves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harrysarson.github.io/portfolio/curves/</guid><description>Click on the screen to create a polynomial curve that will pass through any and all points you chose.
Try using a custom mode for example &amp;lsquo;hyperbolic&amp;rsquo; as shown in the picture to make more interesting curves.</description></item></channel></rss>